JUAN JOSE VANEGAS MAYA

CONTACT INFO

647-568-1890

Juanjovanegas21@gmail.com

210 Victoria St. Toronto

in linkedin.com/in/juan-josevanegas-maya/

juanvmaya.github.io/personalportfolio/

EDUCATION

Advanced Diploma in Electronics Engineering Technology

Seneca College, Toronto, ON September 2017– December 2019

Scholarships / Leadership Awards:

Seneca Student Federation International Student Award and Campus Living Centre Academic.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

ReactJS Figma
JavaScript Python
CSS C

HTMI GitHub

Redux Microsoft Office

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Communication

Building Relationships

Critical Thinking

Innovation

Perseverance

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Result-driven and motivated software developer with demonstrated experience in both business and web software development. Quick learner and easy adopter to new technologies and existing projects. Proven record of collaborating in real-world web applications accountable for \$1.75M in annual revenue.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Electronics Sales Account Manager and Online Ordering SupervisorBittele Electronics Inc, Jan 2020 - Present

- Lead and contributor to the online ordering system, demonstrating success by surpassing the annual sales target by 34.6% (originally \$1.3M) with a record all-time high sales of 1.75M in annual revenue.
- Responsible for quickly and iteratively creating user flows, wireframes, prototypes, and high-fidelity mock-ups for internal sales software-related projects.
- Work in collaboration with the software development team and sales manager to enhance UI and UX, re-architecting and maintaining the online ordering system.
- Technical point of contact for sales prospects and existing clients. Currently
 managing over 620 client accounts. Communicating with 10-20 client
 accounts daily with using tools like powered by CRM and ERP systems.

Senior Research Assistant

Seneca College, July 2019 - October 2020

Worked closely with research project manager and professors in the planning, designing, and prototyping of two research projects:

- A. Universal retrofit system for autonomous control of robotic wet/dry cleaners for client Cyberworks Robotics Inc. (September 2019 October 2020).
- ✓ Responsible for the electronics system for control design and implementation using Arduino, Linux, and ROS (Robot Operating System).
- B. Eco-Friendly, Automatic Equine Water Trough System for Lenka Equestrian Centre. (July 2019 December 2019).
- ✓ Responsible for the electronics system for control design and implementation using Arduino, sensors and solar panel technology.

LANGUAGES & OTHER INTERESTS

- Fluent in English and Spanish.
- Co-Founder and Co-President of the company Uniqoffee Ltd. -Arkaika Coffee in 2018. ArkaikaCoffee.com / @arkaikacoffee!
- Co-founder of the clothing brand Lima Rosa, Colombia, 2019.
 @LimaRosatiendaderopa
- Software development enthusiast: Currently working in a personal portfolio using technologies like Figma, GitHub, HTML, CSS, ReactJS and Firebase.
- Direct contributor to the development of Professor Benjamin Shefler's new course MCO556 – ARM® Microcontroller for Real-time Embedded Applications at Seneca College (2020).